Jose Padron Fernandez



josepadron.go@gmail.com



3103447203



linkedin.com/in/padronjosef



https://padronjose.com/

Summary

React Frontend Developer with 3 years of experience working in different web programming projects and solid knowledge in interface designing (UI).

Knowledge in JavaScript and React. JS, preprocessors such as SaSS & Stylus.

Design of interfaces (UI), with programs like ADOBE XD and FIGMA.

- English C1.
- REACT.
- REDUX.
- BOOTSTRAP.
- NODE JS.
- ADOBE XD, FIGMA.
- COPYWRITING.
- GIT y Git Flow.

Pixel perfect, lifelong learner and tech lover.

- ** Personal Portfolio: https://padronjose.com
- ** GitHub: https://github.com/padronjosef
- ** Behance: https://www.behance.net/josepadron

Experience



Online Community Relations

Platzi

Jun 2020 - Feb 2021 (9 months)

Leading developer communities, UX Interviewing, UI Designing and Create graphic assets.

?

Customer Success Engineer

Platzi

Sep 2019 - Jun 2020 (10 months)

Student Coaching, Create learning paths, Customer Experience and Training peers.

Frontend Developer

Sistemas C3

Jan 2019 - Oct 2019 (10 months)

Create UI interfaces, Develop the designs in functional code and Develop lading pages

CO-FOUNDER & CEO

Gden Technology

Oct 2018 - Dec 2018 (3 months)

Create UI interfaces, Create graphics assets, Develop the designs in functional code and Develop lading pages.

Web Master

SERICINCOL SAS

Sep 2017 - Oct 2018 (1 year 2 months)

Create UI interfaces, Develop the designs in functional code and Develop lading pages.

Education

Santiago Mariño Polytechnic University Institute

Degree in Engineering, Electrical, Electronic and Communications Engineering Technology/Technician 2012 - Present

Licenses & Certifications

- Advanced English Level Centro Venezolano Americano del Zulia. CEVAZ
- Interface design and UX Platzi c23a8962-10f7-4584-b43c-3816c7b07ab2
- Git and GitHub Professional Platzi 4546cf55-a075-4418-94ff-12af94e3a5ac
- Frontend Developer Platzi b826276f-0916-4925-9d17-8c26cf3aca63

Skills

GitHub • React.js • Bootstrap • responsive design • Web Development • Aplicaciones web • UI • HTML5 • Git • JavaScript